{"qid": "0", "question": "Who penned the book Truth, Love, Non-Violence: The Story of Gurcharan Singh Bhatia?", "answer": "Alexis Kienlen"}
{"qid": "1", "question": "Who penned the book Robert Graves the Assault Heroic 19 (v. 1)?", "answer": "Richard Perc Graves"}
{"qid": "2", "question": "Who penned the book Cape Cod Surprise: Oliver Matches Wits with Hurricane Carol?", "answer": "Carol Newman Cronin, Laurie Ann Cronin"}
{"qid": "3", "question": "Do you know who penned the book Sea Monsters and Other Delicacies (An Awfully Beastly Business, #2)?", "answer": "David Sinden, Matthew Morgan, Guy Macdonald"}
{"qid": "4", "question": "Who are the authors of the book Cat Out of the Bag (By the Tail, #1)?", "answer": "Tatiana Caldwell"}
{"qid": "5", "question": "Who are the authors of the book Life in Stone: Fossils of the Colorado Plateau?", "answer": "Christa Sadler"}
{"qid": "6", "question": "Do you know who penned the book An Act of Evil (Augustus Maltravers Mystery Book 1)?", "answer": "Robert    Richardson"}
{"qid": "7", "question": "Can you tell me the authors of the book \u0623\u0648\u0631\u0627\u0642\u064a.. \u062d\u064a\u0627\u062a\u064a.. \u062c1?", "answer": "Nawal El-Saadawi, nwl ls`dwy"}
{"qid": "8", "question": "Can you tell me the authors of the book Don't Panic: The Official Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy Companion?", "answer": "Neil Gaiman"}
{"qid": "9", "question": "Do you know who penned the book The Battle For WondLa (The Search for WondLa, #3)?", "answer": "Tony DiTerlizzi"}
{"qid": "10", "question": "What is the publisher of the book In Colder Blood?", "answer": "Rj Parker Publishing"}
{"qid": "11", "question": "What is the publisher of the book At Home in the World?", "answer": "Picador"}
{"qid": "12", "question": "Jabberwock Jack (Nowak Brothers #2) is published by which company?", "answer": "Createspace Independent Publishing Platform"}
{"qid": "13", "question": "Can you tell me the publisher of the book Como \u00e9 Linda a Puta da Vida?", "answer": "Porto Editora"}
{"qid": "14", "question": "Can you tell me the publisher of the book The World Unseen?", "answer": "Enlightenment Press"}
{"qid": "15", "question": "Can you tell me the publisher of the book May the Best Man Die (Carnegie Kincaid, #3)?", "answer": "Dell"}
{"qid": "16", "question": "Who is the publisher for the book Bomb: The Race to Build\u2014and Steal\u2014the World's Most Dangerous Weapon?", "answer": "Flash Point"}
{"qid": "17", "question": "Can you tell me the publisher of the book Ginger Finds a Home?", "answer": "Candlewick"}
{"qid": "18", "question": "The Boy Next Door is published by which company?", "answer": "The Random House group"}
{"qid": "19", "question": "Who is the publisher for the book The Seasonal Baker: Easy Recipes from My Home Kitchen to Make Year-Round?", "answer": "Clarkson Potter"}
{"qid": "20", "question": "Which shelves do we need to put the book Southwestern Historical Quarterly Volume 1 (Jul 1897 - Apr 1898) on?", "answer": "texas-related, non-fiction, history, educational"}
{"qid": "21", "question": "Where should we put the book Politics and the English Language? On which shelves?", "answer": "to-read, non-fiction, politics, essays, currently-reading, favorites, nonfiction, writing, classics, language, philosophy, books-i-own, linguistics, 20th-century, literature, english, political, owned, orwell, essay, history, read-in-2014, kindle, george-orwell, english-literature, british, owned-books, read-in-2015, read-in-english, criticism, on-writing, uni, languages, favourites, to-buy, british-lit, re-read, my-books, to-read-non-fiction, british-literature, journalism, ebooks, political-science, short-stories, literary-criticism, theory, read-in-2017, lit-crit, classics-to-read, britain, 1940s, european-literature, i-own, read-in-2013, education, sociology, communication, psychology, want-to-read, important, non-fic, book-club, read-for-school, 2016-reads, europe, read-2016, american-politics, politics-philosophy, 4-stars, non-fiction-tbr, nonfic, read-next, read-in-2016, history-politics, english-lit, socialism, male-author, to-read-next, language-communication, my-library, read-2015, reread, classic-literature, other-non-fiction, to-read-again, rated-5, work, brit-lit, non-fiction-read, recommended, 1, unrated, books-about-books, articles-and-essays, english-language, ebook, literary-theory, books-to-buy, university, nonfiction-other"}
{"qid": "22", "question": "On which shelves should we place the book Theo: The Other Van Gogh?", "answer": "to-read, narrative-non-fiction, favorites, arts-all-reference-and-how-to, biography-and-memoir, biography-and-history, biographies, artists-and-art-history, art, i-own, 2012-challenge-books, non-fiction, library-books, personal-library, non-fiction---art-history, non-fiction-biography, somebody-please-get-me-a-copy-"}
{"qid": "23", "question": "Where should we put the book Paranormal Detective (Mona Livelong, #1)? On which shelves?", "answer": "to-read, fiction, currently-reading, horror, black-women-in-horror-writing, consideration, 2017-year-of-the-woman, science-fiction, furry-dead-others, dynamic-women, black-authors-bks, mystery, memorable-lines-passages, black-specfic, yes-yes-yes, s-heros-heros, favorites, favorite-mystery-books, favorite-authors, scifi-fantasy"}
{"qid": "24", "question": "Where should we put the book A cabeza descalza (Biblioteca de Ciencia Ficci\u00f3n, #42)? On which shelves?", "answer": "to-read, science-fiction, sci-fi, currently-reading, sf, fiction, default, post-apocalyptic, owned, favorites, ebooks, sci-fi-fantasy, science, scifi, owned-books, tengo, not-read, ciencia-ficci\u00f3n, drugs, wish-list, english-lit, fantasy, british, to-buy, speculative-fiction, maybe, on-calibre-to-read, have-but-not-read, own-havent-read, to-read-science-fiction-novel, l-ted-gioia-conceptual-fiction, want-to-buy, sci-fi-fantasy-horror, non-challenge, author-more, fictions, 0000-spiral-necklace, date-read, library, lysergic, unread, limbo-unread, 00-theoretical-limits-of-danger, not-now, travel, surreal, doppelg\u00e4nger, poetry, kindle, 2, speculative-literature, new-wave-sf, avant-garde, science-fiction-fantasy, gave-up-on, mass-meerkat, e-books, amazon, kristin-glover, a-a, for-sale, dystopian, apocalyptic-post-apocalyptic, moist-market-paper-bags, authors-a, main, sftr, 1, z-fisico, a-novela-sci-fi, england, fiction-500-master-list, 20th-century-fiction, available, hardcovers-to-get, brian-w-aldiss, a-gnxsta-nip-catlg, non-fiction, zdrugs, to-be-read-shelf, books, maybe-someday, front-bedroom-bookcase, why-not-call-it-poetry, too-sexy-for-maiden-aunts, bokus, birthday-christmas-presents, to-read-fiction, my-books, 1993, s, pdf, serie-azul, collection, own-to-read, good-trips, ciencia-ficcion-fantas\u00eda, other, le-fantastique-a-m, on-the-shelf"}
{"qid": "25", "question": "Which shelves are suitable for placing the book \u0633\u0644\u0627\u062e\u200c\u062e\u0627\u0646\u0647\u200c\u06cc \u0634\u0645\u0627\u0631\u0647\u200c\u06cc \u067e\u0646\u062c?", "answer": "to-read, currently-reading, classics, fiction, favorites, science-fiction, sci-fi, classic, war, owned, literature, historical-fiction, books-i-own, novels, time-travel, favourites, scifi, american, fantasy, to-buy, kindle, satire, 1001-books, vonnegut, humor, owned-books, american-literature, library, school, book-club, adult, novel, historical, literary-fiction, sci-fi-fantasy, wwii, 20th-century, classics-to-read, history, adult-fiction, audiobook, re-read, sf, modern-classics, 1001, banned-books, kurt-vonnegut, general-fiction, kindle-unlimited, audiobooks, ebook, to-re-read, my-library, all-time-favorites, english, classic-literature, american-lit, high-school, contemporary, literary, default, rory-gilmore-reading-challenge, my-books, to-read-classics, ebooks, dystopian, wish-list, favorite-books, dystopia, 1001-books-to-read-before-you-die, world-war-ii, speculative-fiction, classic-fiction, books, audio, read-for-school, ww2, abandoned, to-reread, scifi-fantasy, lit, read-in-2014, to-read-fiction, classic-lit, for-school, read-in-2016, read-in-2015, reread, aliens, audible, postmodern, humour, own-it, i-own, 1960s, favorite, comedy, fantasy-sci-fi, philosophy, read-in-2017"}
{"qid": "26", "question": "Which shelves are suitable for placing the book Limitation: Book I of the Demiseer Saga?", "answer": "to-read"}
{"qid": "27", "question": "Which shelves do we need to put the book Looking for Alibrandi on?", "answer": "to-read, young-adult, ya, favorites, contemporary, australian, fiction, romance, currently-reading, books-i-own, favourites, coming-of-age, australia, aussie, owned, realistic-fiction, family, ya-contemporary, teen, school, stand-alone, realistic, young-adult-fiction, owned-books, chick-lit, australian-author, library, aussie-ya, read-in-2012, high-school, australian-authors, ya-lit, read-for-school, i-own, aussie-authors, made-me-cry, contemporary-fiction, melina-marchetta, friendship, read-in-2014, ya-fiction, contemporary-ya, \u00dda-fiction, australian-fiction, 5-stars, read-in-2013, aussie-author, to-buy, my-books, drama, audiobooks, re-read, read-in-2011, kindle, school-books, audiobook, read-in-2015, ya-books, ya-romance, standalone, ebook, read-in-2016, 4-stars, favorite, on-my-bookshelf, novels, childhood-favourites, ebooks, general-fiction, teen-fiction, young-adults, favourite, standalones, read-2013, wish-list, reviewed, 20th-century, own-it, teenlit, loveozya, read-2015, female-authors, read-in-english, australian-books, default, novel, contemp, book-to-movie, realistic-ya, english, recommended, borrowed, australian-literature, read-2016, 2013-reads, funny, real-life, female-author, childhood, aussie-aussie-aussie"}
{"qid": "28", "question": "Which shelves are designated for the book The Vicar Of Nibbleswicke?", "answer": "to-read, childrens, fiction, children, roald-dahl, children-s, children-s-books, humor, childhood, kids, owned, favorites, books-i-own, young-adult, kids-books, classics, english, short-stories, humour, default, currently-reading, children-s-literature, comedy, childhood-favorites, funny, juvenile-fiction, juvenile, childrens-fiction, middle-grade, ya, british, library, childhood-books, fantasy, childhood-reads, dahl, childrens-books, dyslexia, children-s-lit, short-story, illustrated, children-s-fiction, childrens-lit, i-own, junior-fiction, classroom-library, children-s-book, ebooks, 1990s, owned-books, to-buy, youth-fiction, children-books, children-young-adult, kid-stuff, read-2016, read-in-2015, 20th-century, read-in-2014, borrowed, humorous, literature, my-books, kindle, kinderboeken, books-from-my-childhood, picture-book, transitional-chapter-books, favorite-authors, read-aloud, not-read, my-collection, chapter-books, kid-books, in-america, novels, my-library, read-in-2016, religion, literacy, after-easy-readers, need, d, children-s-picture-books, books-for-kids, children-s-young-adult, language, to-get, my-childhood, picture-books, ragazzi, fantastic, middle-school, ebook, read-2012, books, books-from-childhood, lol, read-as-a-child, for-kids"}
{"qid": "29", "question": "Which shelves do we need to put the book First Year Healthy on?", "answer": "to-read, graphic-novels, comics, graphic-novel, fiction, comix, graphic-novels-comics, art, read-in-2015, comics-graphic-novels, library, surrealism, favorites, read-in-2016, to-read-graphic-novels, comic, fantasy, owned, comic-books, read-2016, 2010s, art-comics, graphic-novels-etc, trippy, romance, crime, graphic, mental-illness, mental-health, comics-and-graphic-novels, adult-fiction, canada, read-graphic-novels, graphicnovel, read-in-2017, gn-comics, surrealist, read-library, kindle-books, adult, currently-reading, bettendorf-library, public-library, graphics-standalone-and-series, good-but-not-my-thing, novels, 2017-ideas, dysfunctional, comics-graphic-novels-to-read, nypl, blob-comics, rad-comics, cartoony-things, 1-2016, health, pdf, school-library, 21st-century, indie-comics, wish-list, books-that-i-read-in-2016, comics-alt, graphic-literature, sequential-art, aadl, comics-graphic-novels-manga, i-love-the-library, books-by-men, wrc-reading-is-my-cup-of-tea, springbreak2016, 2016-read, gn-short-stories, 2016-reading-challenge, glbtq, gay, read-own, best-comic-art-2015, setting-north-america, protag-female, lit-canadian, author-poc, author-male, art-relevant, favorite-reading-2015, 2016-ideas, comics-to-read, fairytale-folklore, koyama-picturebox-buenaventura, favorites-sequential-art, eisner-harvey-ignatz-etc-awards, disturbing-art-and-literature, canadian, gn-psych, gn-crime, graphic-novels-and-comics, plano-library, books-i-own, art-graphic-novel, graphics-comics, sex"}
{"qid": "30", "question": "Can you tell me the genre of the book Prayer on a Wing (On A Wing, #2)?", "answer": "fantasy, paranormal, romance"}
{"qid": "31", "question": "Can you tell me the genre of the book KEIR & MYAH?", "answer": "romance, fiction"}
{"qid": "32", "question": "What genre does the book Dark Stallions (Legend of the Centaurians #1) belong to?", "answer": "fantasy, paranormal, young-adult"}
{"qid": "33", "question": "Could you inform me about the genre classification of the book \u039c\u03b1\u03c4\u03c9\u03bc\u03ad\u03bd\u03bf\u03c2 \u0393\u03ac\u03bc\u03bf\u03c2?", "answer": "poetry, fiction, romance, history, historical fiction, biography"}
{"qid": "34", "question": "Could you inform me about the genre classification of the book 17 cerita terbaik ernest hemingway?", "answer": "fiction"}
{"qid": "35", "question": "Can you tell me the genre of the book The Way We Live Now?", "answer": "non-fiction, fiction"}
{"qid": "36", "question": "Can you tell me the genre of the book The Silver Metal Lover (Silver Metal Lover, #1)?", "answer": "fiction, fantasy, paranormal, romance, young-adult"}
{"qid": "37", "question": "What genre does the book Marvel Now! Point One #1 belong to?", "answer": "comics, graphic"}
{"qid": "38", "question": "Do you know the literary genre of the book Renungan Kloset: Dari Cengkeh Sampai Utrecht: Kumpulan Puisi?", "answer": "poetry, young-adult"}
{"qid": "39", "question": "What genre does the book Bonsai belong to?", "answer": "fiction, romance"}
{"qid": "40", "question": "Which series includes the book Demelza (Poldark, #2)?", "answer": "The Poldark Saga"}
{"qid": "41", "question": "In which series is the book His To Keep (His and Hers Book 4) included?", "answer": "His and Hers"}
{"qid": "42", "question": "Which series includes the book Dealing with Denver?", "answer": "Barbourville"}
{"qid": "43", "question": "Which series includes the book \u0414\u0435\u0442\u0441\u0442\u0432\u043e?", "answer": "Autobiography"}
{"qid": "44", "question": "The book Queen of Song and Souls is part of which series?", "answer": "Tairen Soul"}
{"qid": "45", "question": "What series does the book The Fatal Frails belong to?", "answer": "Johnny Killain"}
{"qid": "46", "question": "What series does the book Demon's Destiny (Lords of The Underworld, #10) belong to?", "answer": "Lords of the Underworld"}
{"qid": "47", "question": "The book Legend Of Zelda: The Ocarina Of Time Vol. 2 is part of which series?", "answer": "The Legend of Zelda"}
{"qid": "48", "question": "In which series is the book Viento y joyas included?", "answer": "El Dia del Watusi"}
{"qid": "49", "question": "The book Loving Hart (The Hart Family, #3) is part of which series?", "answer": "The Hart Family"}
{"qid": "50", "question": "What is the publication year of the book Tai-Pan  Part 2 Of 2?", "answer": "2000"}
{"qid": "51", "question": "When was the book The Very Best of Productive Muslim put into print?", "answer": "2010"}
{"qid": "52", "question": "What year was the book Eco Dog: Healthy Living for Your Pet first published?", "answer": "2008"}
{"qid": "53", "question": "What year was the book Beowulf: A New Translation for Oral Delivery first published?", "answer": "2007"}
{"qid": "54", "question": "In what year was the book \u6ca1\u6709\u4eba\u7ed9\u4ed6\u5199\u4fe1\u7684\u4e0a\u6821 published?", "answer": "2013"}
{"qid": "55", "question": "What is the publication year of the book Soul Surfer, Study Guide?", "answer": "2011"}
{"qid": "56", "question": "In what year was the book Eternal Pleasure (Gods of the Night, #1) published?", "answer": "2008"}
{"qid": "57", "question": "What year was the book The Legendary Lord (Playful Brides, #6) first published?", "answer": "2016"}
{"qid": "58", "question": "When did the book Harmleikur \u00ed H\u00e9\u00f0insfir\u00f0i make its first publication?", "answer": "2009"}
{"qid": "59", "question": "When was the book Asian American Dreams: The Emergence of an American People put into print?", "answer": "2001"}
{"qid": "60", "question": "How many pages are contained in the book Inu Yasha, Volume 1?", "answer": "184"}
{"qid": "61", "question": "What is the page count of the book Pandemonium: Devourer of Souls?", "answer": "18"}
{"qid": "62", "question": "How many pages does the book The Execution of Noa P. Singleton have?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "63", "question": "How many pages are contained in the book Lord Edgware Dies (Hercule Poirot, #9)?", "answer": "242"}
{"qid": "64", "question": "How many pages are contained in the book Longing For Love (Gansett Island Series, #7)?", "answer": "369"}
{"qid": "65", "question": "How many pages are contained in the book The Road to Paradise (Paradise #3)?", "answer": "314"}
{"qid": "66", "question": "How many pages are contained in the book When They Shine Brightest?", "answer": "264"}
{"qid": "67", "question": "Can you tell me the number of pages in the book The Rough Guide to Shanghai 1?", "answer": "208"}
{"qid": "68", "question": "Can you tell me the number of pages in the book Murder in the Latin Quarter (Aimee Leduc Investigations, #9)?", "answer": "317"}
{"qid": "69", "question": "How many pages does the book The Life of Henri Brulard have?", "answer": "361"}
{"qid": "70", "question": "Does the book Blood Slave come in an eBook format?", "answer": "true"}
{"qid": "71", "question": "Is Resource Wars: The New Landscape of Global Conflict available as an eBook version?", "answer": "false"}
{"qid": "72", "question": "Is the book Dead of Winter (DCI Andrew Fenwick #5) an eBook?", "answer": "false"}
{"qid": "73", "question": "Can the book The Accidental Courier be accessed as an eBook?", "answer": "false"}
{"qid": "74", "question": "Can the book La Voisine be accessed as an eBook?", "answer": "true"}
{"qid": "75", "question": "Is the book I'll Trade My Peanut-Butter Sandwich an eBook?", "answer": "true"}
{"qid": "76", "question": "Is The Steps We Took available as an eBook version?", "answer": "false"}
{"qid": "77", "question": "Is the book A Hidden Truth an eBook?", "answer": "false"}
{"qid": "78", "question": "Does the book \u0417\u0430\u0438\u0440 come in an eBook format?", "answer": "false"}
{"qid": "79", "question": "Does the book Nathan's Story come in an eBook format?", "answer": "false"}
{"qid": "80", "question": "Can you tell me the language in which the book Do Your Laundry or You'll Die Alone is written?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "81", "question": "The book \u062f\u0644\u064a\u0644 \u0625\u0646\u0634\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0634\u0631\u0648\u0639\u0627\u062a \u0627\u0644\u0635\u063a\u064a\u0631\u0629 is written in what language?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "82", "question": "In which language is the book Jupitervale: Special Edition composed?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "83", "question": "Can you tell me the language in which the book La meraviglia degli anni imperfetti is written?", "answer": "ita"}
{"qid": "84", "question": "The book Plus rien qu'un souvenir (La Douleur Fant\u00f4me, #1) is written in what language?", "answer": "fre"}
{"qid": "85", "question": "The book Mad Lizard Mambo (Kai Gracen, #2) is written in what language?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "86", "question": "The book Hiro\u015fima Sevgilim is written in what language?", "answer": "tur"}
{"qid": "87", "question": "Can you tell me the language in which the book Desire for Three (Desire, Oklahoma, #1) is written?", "answer": "en-GB"}
{"qid": "88", "question": "In what language is the book Call Me Cat (Call Me Cat Trilogy, #1) authored?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "89", "question": "What language is the book Goofy's Big Race (Walt Disney Fun-to-Read Library, #4) written in?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "90", "question": "Search for books authored by the same person and published by the same entity as the book L'uomo scomparso?", "answer": "Suspense, Lo scheletro che balla"}
{"qid": "91", "question": "Are there any books by the same author and from the same publisher as the book V Is for Virgin?", "answer": "Cinder & Ella (Cinder & Ella, #1), Remember Jamie Baker (Jamie Baker, #3), The Avery Shaw Experiment, Cinder & Ella, The Libby Garrett Intervention, Serial Hottie, More Than Jamie Baker (Jamie Baker, #2), The Avery Shaw Experiment (Science Squad, #1), Chameleon (Supernaturals, #1), Ungifted (Supernaturals, #2), Joni, Underway, V is for Virgin (V is for Virgin, #1), Being Jamie Baker (Jamie Baker, #1), Happily \u200bEver After (Cinder & Ella, #2)"}
{"qid": "92", "question": "Are there any books by the same author and from the same publisher as the book Pathologies?", "answer": "Ampersand, Mass., Questionstruck: A Collection of Question-Based Texts Derived from the Books of Calvin Trillin, Keyhole 6"}
{"qid": "93", "question": "Are there any books by the same author and from the same publisher as the book The Fires of Merlin (The Lost Years of Merlin, #3)?", "answer": "The Lost Years of Merlin (The Lost Years of Merlin, #1), The Wings of Merlin (The Lost Years of Merlin, #5), Ghost Hands, The Wisdom of Merlin: 7 Magical Words for a Meaningful Life, Atlantis Lost (Atlantis, #3), The Merlin Effect (The Adventures of Kate, #3), Child of the Dark Prophecy (The Great Tree of Avalon, #1), Tree Girl, The Seven Songs of Merlin (The Lost Years of Merlin, #2), The Mirror of Merlin (The Lost Years of Merlin, #4), Atlantis Rising (Atlantis, #1), Atlantis in Peril (Atlantis, #2)"}
{"qid": "94", "question": "Search for books authored by the same person and published by the same entity as the book Rumble on the Bayou?", "answer": "Swamp Team 3, Resurrection in Mudbug (Ghost-in-Law #4), Trouble in Mudbug, Lethal Bayou Beauty"}
{"qid": "95", "question": "Can you identify books with the same author and publisher as the book L'Am\u00e9nagement du territoire?", "answer": "La Th\u00e9orie de l'information"}
{"qid": "96", "question": "Can you identify books with the same author and publisher as the book Don't Look Down?", "answer": "Essondale, Slide in all Direction"}
{"qid": "97", "question": "Search for books authored by the same person and published by the same entity as the book Where Does The Weirdness Go?: Why Quantum Mechanics Is Strange, But Not As Strange As You Think?", "answer": "Science Of Jurassic Park And The Lost World: Or, How To Build A Dinosaur"}
{"qid": "98", "question": "Search for books authored by the same person and published by the same entity as the book Maps of the Disney Parks: Charting 60 Years from California to Shanghai?", "answer": "The Ultimate Disney Trivia Book 3: 999 New Questions!"}
{"qid": "99", "question": "Are there any books by the same author and from the same publisher as the book All the Light We Cannot See?", "answer": "The Shell Collector: Stories, Memory Wall, About Grace"}
{"qid": "100", "question": "Could you help me find books by the same author and of the same genre as Sweet?", "answer": "Sweet: Desserts from London's Ottolenghi, Jerusalem, Plenty: Vibrant Vegetable Recipes from London's Ottolenghi, Ottolenghi: The Cookbook, Genussvoll Vegetarisch: mediterran, Orientalisch, Raffiniert, Plenty: Vibrant Recipes from London's Ottolenghi, Plenty More: Vibrant Vegetable Cooking from London's Ottolenghi, Plenty, NOPI: The Cookbook, Jerusalem: A Cookbook, Ottolenghi, Plenty More"}
{"qid": "101", "question": "Could you help me find books by the same author and of the same genre as It Feels So Good When I Stop?", "answer": "Meat is Murder, Pernice to Me, Esta canci\u00f3n me recuerda a m\u00ed, Smiths' Meat is Murder: 5 (33 1/3)"}
{"qid": "102", "question": "Can you suggest books by the same author and within the same genre as the book Justification by Grace Through Faith: Finding Freedom from Legalism, Lawlessness, Pride, and Despair?", "answer": "The Major Works"}
{"qid": "103", "question": "Find books by the same author and share similar genre with book \u0418\u043d\u0442\u0435\u0440\u043d\u0435\u0442-\u043c\u0430\u0440\u043a\u0435\u0442\u0438\u043d\u0433. \u041b\u0443\u0447\u0448\u0438\u0435 \u0431\u0435\u0441\u043f\u043b\u0430\u0442\u043d\u044b\u0435 \u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442\u044b?", "answer": "Free Marketing: 101 Low and No-Cost Ways to Grow Your Business, Online and Off"}
{"qid": "104", "question": "Find books by the same author and share similar genre with book Come allestire le luci per uno studio fotografico in casa?", "answer": "How to Set Up Photography Lighting for a Home Studio, County Fair Blue Ribbon Winning Cookbook: Main Dish, Casserole, & Vegetable Recipes (Volume 1), Pest Control for Organic Gardening: Natural Methods for Pest and Disease Control, Come prendervi cura del vostro coniglio e come scegliere le migliori razze da compagnia, Come migliorare le condizioni del terreno nel vostro giardino, How To Improve Soil Condition in Your Garden, A Coloring Book for Adults: Remember the Joy of Coloring and Reduce Stress (Volume 1), Make Your Own Essential Oils from Raw Plants: Using Oils & Herbs for Optimum Health, Everything about Rabbits:  Including an Exhaustive List of Rabbit Breeds, Preserve Your Family Pictures: How To Save Photo Heirlooms for Future Generations, A Book of Dog Breeds for Children:: They Are All Dogs, A Book of Dog Breeds For Children:: They're All Dogs, How to Care for Your Pet Rabbits: Including Choosing the Best Breeds for Pets, Il Libro Delle Razze Canine Per Bambini - Sono Tutti Cani, Alaska - Travelogue by State: Experience Both the Ordinary and Obscure (Exploring America Series Book 1)"}
{"qid": "105", "question": "Could you help me find books by the same author and of the same genre as Humiliation?", "answer": "Repentance (Empire Saga, #5; Space Empire Trilogy, #2), Sanctification (Empire saga, #6; Space Empire Trilogy, #3), The Space Empire Saga: City on a Hill / Sojourner / Humiliation / Repentance / Sanctification"}
{"qid": "106", "question": "What other books, from the same author and genre, can you recommend that are similar to The Winter Palace?", "answer": "Empress of the Night: A Novel of Catherine the Great, Die Zarin der Nacht (Catherine, #2), Dancing With Kings, Il palazzo d'inverno, The Chosen Maiden, The Winter Palace: A Novel of Catherine the Great (Catherine, #1), Die Schwester des T\u00e4nzers, The Winter Palace: A Novel of Catherine the Great, In Het Winterpaleis: een Roman van Catharina de Grote, The Winter Palace: A Novel Of Catherine The Great, Necessary Lies, In het Winterpaleis, Garden of Venus, Der Winterpalast, Die Zarin der Nacht, O Pal\u00e1cio de Inverno (Catherine, #1), Katarzyna Wielka. Gra o w\u0142adz\u0119, Empress of the Night (Catherine, #2), Empress of the Night, Zimski dvorac"}
{"qid": "107", "question": "Can you suggest books by the same author and within the same genre as the book The Creative Writing Handbook: Techniques For New Writers?", "answer": "On Acting: Interviews with Actors, The Drama Handbook: A Guide to Reading Plays, The Creative Writing Workbook"}
{"qid": "108", "question": "Could you help me find books by the same author and of the same genre as Coq De Combat (Shamo, #2)?", "answer": "\u8ecd\u9d8f 5 [Shamo] (Shamo, #5), Fire Investigator Nanase Vol. 1, Shamo Volume 30, Coq De Combat, Tome 3 (Shamo, #3), Glaucos, Tome 4, Glaucos 02, Glaucos 03, Coq De Combat, Tome 1 (Shamo, #1), Glaucos, Tome 1, Coq De Combat, Tome 4 (Shamo, #4), Shamo, Band 16 (Shamo, #16)"}
{"qid": "109", "question": "Find books by the same author and share similar genre with book Braeton & Drew (Something About Him, #4)?", "answer": "Loving Josie (Torey Hope #4), Ryker & Gavin (Something About Him, #5), Kendrick (Torey Hope: The Later Years, #4), Barrett & Ivan (Something About Him, #3), Bryan & Jase, The Beginning (Something About Him, #0.5), Kade & Cameron (Something About Him, #6), Sawyer (Torey Hope: The Later Years #2), Bryan & Jase (Something About Him, #1 ), Christmas in Torey Hope: A Novella (Torey Hope #3), Loving Josie, A Torey Hope Novel, Eli & Gage: Something About Him: A Valentine's Day Short Story, Zach (Torey Hope: The Later Years, #3), Because of Beckett (Torey Hope #2), Barrett & Ivan, Fight For It (The Blueridge Junction Boys, #1), Eli & Gage: Something About Him, For Nicky (Torey Hope #1), Sawyer (Torey Hope: The Later Years, #2), Decker (Torey Hope: The Later Years #1), Something About Him: 6 Book Box Set, Zach (Torey Hope: The Later Years #3), Decker (Torey Hope: The Later Years, #1), Brody & Nick (Something About Him, #2), Devoted, Bryan & Jase"}
{"qid": "110", "question": "Find the earliest book written by the author of the book Saving Gideon (Clover Ridge #1)?", "answer": "Brodie's Bride"}
{"qid": "111", "question": "Can you tell me the earliest book that the author of Indecision (Maine Attraction #1) wrote?", "answer": "Rumor Has It (Limelight, #1)"}
{"qid": "112", "question": "What was the first book ever written by the same author as The Highland Henchman (Highland Force, #2)?", "answer": "Koicto"}
{"qid": "113", "question": "What is the first book written by the author who penned the book Wyreth's Flame?", "answer": "Blood Will Tell (Chimeria #1)"}
{"qid": "114", "question": "Can you tell me the earliest book that the author of \u03a3\u03ba\u03ad\u03c4\u03b7 \u03b1\u03bd\u03b1\u03c1\u03c7\u03af\u03b1 wrote?", "answer": "\u0627\u0641\u0627\u062f\u0647 \u0627\u06cc \u0647\u0627, \u039f \u03b3\u03b5\u03bb\u03c9\u03c4\u03bf\u03c0\u03bf\u03b9\u03cc\u03c2"}
{"qid": "115", "question": "What is the first book written by the author who penned the book The Art of the Possible?", "answer": "Living Beautifully Together"}
{"qid": "116", "question": "What is the first book written by the author who penned the book Divine By Blood (Partholon, #3)?", "answer": "Voorbestemd (Het Huis van de Nacht, #9)"}
{"qid": "117", "question": "What was the first book ever written by the same author as Star Trek Archives: Best of Peter David (Star Trek Archives, #1)?", "answer": "Knight Life (Modern Arthur, #1), World's Finest, Godzilla: Past, Present, and Future"}
{"qid": "118", "question": "Can you tell me the earliest book that the author of Bear Naked wrote?", "answer": "The Wallflower (Halle Pumas, #1)"}
{"qid": "119", "question": "What was the first book ever written by the same author as Absolution?", "answer": "Wolfbaene"}
{"qid": "120", "question": "What are the other series by the same author as the book Life in the Lucky Zone (The Zone, #2) but not the same as the book's series?", "answer": "The Zone"}
{"qid": "121", "question": "Find the series in which the same author as the book Haunted has contributed, but the series is different from the book's series.", "answer": "Swamp Thing UK, The Mammoth Book of Best New Horror, David Ash, Swamp Thing, Volume I, Rats"}
{"qid": "122", "question": "Identify the series different from the one of the book Hand of Isis (Numinous World, #3) but written by the same author.", "answer": "SGX, The Order of the Air, Stargate SG-1 Chronological, Stargate Atlantis: Legacy, Stargate Atlantis, Travelers' Tales, Numinous World, Stargate SG-1"}
{"qid": "123", "question": "Can you name the series written by the same author of the book Dame tu coraz\u00f3n which are not the book's series?", "answer": "Nightmare Magazine, The Mammoth Book of Ghost Stories, The Gothic Saga, Selected Shorts, The Year's Finest Crime and Mystery Stories, The Mammoth Book of Best New Horror, Hot Blood, New Fairy Tales, The Paris Review Interviews, Gran Super Terror, Best American Essays, The World's Finest Mystery and Crime Stories, The Best American Mystery Stories, Wonderland Quartet, The Dark Descent, Manhattan Noir, The Year's Best Fantasy and Horror, The Best American Short Stories, The Oxford Books of..., Great American Ghost Stories, Transgressions, The Granta Book of the American Short Story, The Southern Vampire Mysteries (short stories and novellas), Den of Shadows, The Snow White, Blood Red Anthology Series, Sisters in Crime, McSweeney's Quarterly Concern, Saga of the Skolian Empire, Ellery Queen Mystery Magazine, L.A. Noire: The Collected Stories"}
{"qid": "124", "question": "Identify the series different from the one of the book Timequake but written by the same author.", "answer": "The Last Interview, Exile trilogy, Ultimate Monster, Spisanie ,,Tera fantastika\", Galaxy Reader, Favorite Science Fiction Stories, Antologia Sci fi, Bruguera libro amigo, The Granta Book of the American Short Story, The Complete Stories of Theodore Sturgeon, The Paris Review Interviews, Best American Nonrequired Reading"}
{"qid": "125", "question": "Which series, unlike the book Aurora's series, are from the same author?", "answer": "Tales from Beyond the Veil, Shadowlands, The Darkling Saga, Crimson, Dreams and Shards Series, Pendragon Chronicles"}
{"qid": "126", "question": "Can you name the series written by the same author of the book Sarah's Birthday which are not the book's series?", "answer": "Fien en Milo"}
{"qid": "127", "question": "Which series, unlike the book Poe at the Gates (Secret Society Girl, #2.3)'s series, are from the same author?", "answer": "13 Tales, For Darkness Shows the Stars, Moth, Secret Society Girl, Generation Dead, The Forest of Hands and Teeth, Uglies, Omega City, Innkeeper's World, Bigfoot Trilogy, The World of Riverside, Killer Unicorns, The Dresden Files, Vampire Academy, The Hunger Games Companions, Caden Butcher"}
{"qid": "128", "question": "Identify the series different from the one of the book Summer Nights but written by the same author.", "answer": "Marked"}
{"qid": "129", "question": "Find the series in which the same author as the book Siapakah John F. Kennedy? has contributed, but the series is different from the book's series.", "answer": "The Doll Shop, Who Was/Is...?, What was..."}
{"qid": "130", "question": "How many works of literature has Cynthia Rowley produced?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "131", "question": "How many works of literature has Gerrie Nelson produced?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "132", "question": "What is the total number of books written by Lawrence M. Wallack?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "133", "question": "How many works of literature has Thierry Gioux produced?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "134", "question": "What is the total number of books written by Connie Barlow?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "135", "question": "How many works of literature has Cathy Ann Johnson produced?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "136", "question": "How many works of literature has Cecilia Piras produced?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "137", "question": "What is the total number of books written by Sarah Fain?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "138", "question": "Can you tell me the number of books George Stimson has penned?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "139", "question": "Can you tell me the number of books Savanna Lee has penned?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "140", "question": "Can you tell me the number of books similar to The Heartbreakers (The Heartbreakers Chronicles, #1)?", "answer": "18"}
{"qid": "141", "question": "Can you tell me the number of books similar to Good Earth?", "answer": "18"}
{"qid": "142", "question": "How many books resemble the book Cadbury Creme Murder (Donut Hole Mystery #3)?", "answer": "16"}
{"qid": "143", "question": "How many books resemble the book Maxims?", "answer": "17"}
{"qid": "144", "question": "What is the count of books similar to the book Kartun Ekonomi, Jilid Satu: Mikroekonomi?", "answer": "15"}
{"qid": "145", "question": "What is the count of books similar to the book Batman '66 Meets the Green Hornet?", "answer": "17"}
{"qid": "146", "question": "How many books resemble the book A History of Zionism?", "answer": "16"}
{"qid": "147", "question": "How many books resemble the book Thomas (Jaded Gentlemen #1)?", "answer": "14"}
{"qid": "148", "question": "How many books resemble the book An Isolated Range (Range, #5)?", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "149", "question": "What is the count of books similar to the book Demonit?", "answer": "16"}
{"qid": "150", "question": "How many books are published by the publisher Real Yayinlari?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "151", "question": "Can you tell me the number of books Valkhoff has published?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "152", "question": "What is the total number of books published by After Hours Publishing?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "153", "question": "Can you tell me the number of books Srpska knjizevna zadruga has published?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "154", "question": "How many books are published by the publisher ntshrt nshr `lm?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "155", "question": "How many books does publisher RUMI publish?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "156", "question": "How many books does publisher 5 zvezdi publish?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "157", "question": "How many books are published by the publisher Sports Illustrated Books?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "158", "question": "How many books does publisher Gagasmedia publish?", "answer": "24"}
{"qid": "159", "question": "What is the total number of books published by Signet (NY)?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "160", "question": "Can you tell me the total number of books in the Cindy Eller series?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "161", "question": "What is the number of books in the series Alpennia?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "162", "question": "How many books are part of the series Naughty Adventures of Angel Knott?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "163", "question": "Can you tell me the total number of books in the The Selection series?", "answer": "12"}
{"qid": "164", "question": "What is the number of books in the series Maisy?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "165", "question": "What is the number of books in the series Descender (single issues)?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "166", "question": "How many books are part of the series Invocacion?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "167", "question": "Can you tell me the total number of books in the X-Factor, Volume III series?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "168", "question": "How many books are part of the series The Henchmen MC?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "169", "question": "How many volumes are in the The Noon Universe series?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "170", "question": "How many authors have teamed up with Anton Nazzal & Sons for publishing?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "171", "question": "Can you tell me the total number of authors who have joined forces with the publisher Sichuan Children's Publishing House?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "172", "question": "Can you tell me the total number of authors who have joined forces with the publisher Commoner's Publishing?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "173", "question": "What is the number of authors who have worked with the publisher Emond?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "174", "question": "What is the number of authors who have worked with the publisher Borherhoff en Lamberigts?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "175", "question": "How many authors have collaborated with the publisher Milt Mays?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "176", "question": "What is the number of authors who have worked with the publisher Club Lighhouse?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "177", "question": "How many authors have collaborated with the publisher Dagonas?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "178", "question": "How many authors have collaborated with the publisher Christel Gottert Verlag?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "179", "question": "Can you tell me the total number of authors who have joined forces with the publisher Blue Star Press Inc?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "180", "question": "Who has written the most books in the same genre as Murray Louis On Dance?", "answer": "Agatha Christie"}
{"qid": "181", "question": "Who has written the most books in the same genre as No Way Out?", "answer": "Agatha Christie"}
{"qid": "182", "question": "Who is the author with the highest number of published books that fall into the same genre as Coyote Willows?", "answer": "Agatha Christie"}
{"qid": "183", "question": "Which writer has the most books of the same genre as Surfeit of Lampreys published?", "answer": "Agatha Christie"}
{"qid": "184", "question": "Who is the author with the highest number of published books that fall into the same genre as Macbeth?", "answer": "Agatha Christie"}
{"qid": "185", "question": "Which author has the most published books that have the same genre as the book The Murder King's Summons (Murder Tales 2)?", "answer": "Stephen King"}
{"qid": "186", "question": "Who is the author with the highest number of published books that fall into the same genre as Phares?", "answer": "Anonymous"}
{"qid": "187", "question": "Can you name the author who has the maximum published books in the same category as Graced?", "answer": "Stephen King"}
{"qid": "188", "question": "Can you name the author who has the maximum published books in the same category as The Esoteric Path of Marriage: A Guide To Spiritual Enlightenment Through Relationship?", "answer": "Anonymous"}
{"qid": "189", "question": "Which writer has the most books of the same genre as The Notorious Byrd Brothers published?", "answer": "Anonymous"}
{"qid": "190", "question": "What is the most common publication format of books by author John Anthony Gilvey?", "answer": "Hardcover"}
{"qid": "191", "question": "What is the predominant publication format for books written by jsm lfrs?", "answer": "ebook"}
{"qid": "192", "question": "What format of publication is most frequently used by Hans Pfeiffer for his/her books?", "answer": "Hardcover"}
{"qid": "193", "question": "What is the most common publication format of books by author Gloria Gaither?", "answer": "ebook"}
{"qid": "194", "question": "What is the most common publication format of books by author Hadiyya Hussein?", "answer": "Paperback"}
{"qid": "195", "question": "What is the most common publication format of books by author George Chandos Bidwell?", "answer": "Paperback"}
{"qid": "196", "question": "What is the most common publication format of books by author Trish Flannery?", "answer": "Paperback"}
{"qid": "197", "question": "What is the usual format in which books by Sara Pitzer are published?", "answer": "Paperback"}
{"qid": "198", "question": "What is the usual format in which books by nj~ lbT@ are published?", "answer": "Paperback"}
{"qid": "199", "question": "What format of publication is most frequently used by Shereen McKellar for his/her books?", "answer": "Paperback"}
{"qid": "200", "question": "In the writings of the author Alan C. Ashton, which genre appears the most?", "answer": "non-fiction"}
{"qid": "201", "question": "What is the dominant genre in the literary works of Tara Calahan King?", "answer": "children"}
{"qid": "202", "question": "Which genre prevails in the portfolio of the author Terence Peter Scully?", "answer": "history, historical fiction, biography"}
{"qid": "203", "question": "Which genre prevails in the portfolio of the author Jacqueline Balcells?", "answer": "children"}
{"qid": "204", "question": "What is the most frequent genre in the works of the author Sienna Bishop?", "answer": "romance"}
{"qid": "205", "question": "What is the dominant genre in the literary works of Alice Jamieson?", "answer": "non-fiction"}
{"qid": "206", "question": "What is the most frequent genre in the works of the author Robert Kleinschroth?", "answer": "non-fiction"}
{"qid": "207", "question": "What is the dominant genre in the literary works of Helen DePrima?", "answer": "romance"}
{"qid": "208", "question": "In the writings of the author Michael  Samuels, which genre appears the most?", "answer": "non-fiction"}
{"qid": "209", "question": "What is the most frequent genre in the works of the author Aris Santoso?", "answer": "history, historical fiction, biography"}
{"qid": "210", "question": "Which publication house has published the highest number of books in the mystery, thriller, crime genre?", "answer": "Brilliance Audio"}
{"qid": "211", "question": "Who is the primary publisher for most books in the young-adult field?", "answer": "HarperCollins"}
{"qid": "212", "question": "Who is the primary publisher for most books in the history, historical fiction, biography field?", "answer": "Penguin Books"}
{"qid": "213", "question": "Which publication house has published the highest number of books in the poetry genre?", "answer": "Penguin Classics"}
{"qid": "214", "question": "Who is the primary publisher for most books in the comics, graphic field?", "answer": "Marvel"}
{"qid": "215", "question": "Which publisher has released the majority of books in the genre romance?", "answer": "Harlequin"}
{"qid": "216", "question": "Who is the primary publisher for most books in the fiction field?", "answer": "HarperCollins"}
{"qid": "217", "question": "Which publisher has released the majority of books in the genre fantasy, paranormal?", "answer": "Createspace Independent Publishing Platform"}
{"qid": "218", "question": "In the genre of children, which publisher has put out the most books?", "answer": "HarperCollins"}
{"qid": "219", "question": "Which publisher has released the majority of books in the genre non-fiction?", "answer": "Oxford University Press, USA"}
{"qid": "220", "question": "What is the predominant language in the books written by Anne M Gray?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "221", "question": "In which language has E.J. Tett most frequently written their books?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "222", "question": "What is the predominant language in the books written by Devin C. Manzullo-Thomas?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "223", "question": "Which language is most often used in books by Claire Mulligan?", "answer": "fre"}
{"qid": "224", "question": "What is the most common language among the books written by author bn mqntyyr?", "answer": "heb"}
{"qid": "225", "question": "Which language is most often used in books by Rui Paulo da Cruz?", "answer": "por"}
{"qid": "226", "question": "What is the most common language among the books written by author Mortaza Motahari [mrtDy mThry]?", "answer": "ara"}
{"qid": "227", "question": "What is the most common language among the books written by author Jade Sylvan?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "228", "question": "What is the primary language of the books that Travis Alabanza has written?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "229", "question": "In which language has Paul  Combs most frequently written their books?", "answer": "eng"}
{"qid": "230", "question": "What book should be recommended to the user based on his history: ['A Man Called Ove', 'I See You', 'The Kitchen House', 'The Immortal Life of Henrietta Lacks', 'A Stranger in the House']?", "answer": "The Missing"}
{"qid": "231", "question": "What book should be recommended to the user based on his history: ['The Little Prince', \"Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (Harry Potter, #1)\", 'City of Bones (The Mortal Instruments, #1)', 'Romeo and Juliet']?", "answer": "Fifty Shades of Grey (Fifty Shades, #1)"}
{"qid": "232", "question": "What book should be recommended to the user based on his history: ['Hungry for You (Argeneau #14)', 'Exposing Casey', 'The Christmas Cookie Club', 'Crunch Time', 'Vamparazzi (Esther Diamond, #4)']?", "answer": "A Dragon's Heart"}
{"qid": "233", "question": "What book should be recommended to the user based on his history: ['Daughter of Smoke & Bone (Daughter of Smoke & Bone, #1)', \"Don't Look Back\"]?", "answer": "When Dimple Met Rishi"}
{"qid": "234", "question": "What book should be recommended to the user based on his history: ['Storm Front (The Dresden Files, #1)', \"From Julia Child's Kitchen\"]?", "answer": "Down These Strange Streets"}
{"qid": "235", "question": "What book should be recommended to the user based on his history: ['Lyndon B. Johnson (The American Presidents, #36)', 'Jimmy Carter (The American Presidents, #39)', 'John F. Kennedy (The American Presidents, #35)', 'Bow Down to Willingham: How White Guilt Enabled a Secretly Malicious Coach to Destroy the Once-Mighty Washington Huskies', 'American Colonies: The Settling of North America']?", "answer": "Chester A. Arthur, A Quarter-century Of Machine Politics"}
{"qid": "236", "question": "What book should be recommended to the user based on his history: ['Annie and the Old One', 'Unstoppable Me!: 10 Ways to Soar Through Life']?", "answer": "J.R.R. Tolkien: Architect of Middle Earth"}
{"qid": "237", "question": "What book should be recommended to the user based on his history: ['Being Mortal: Medicine and What Matters in the End', 'When Breath Becomes Air', 'Saga, Vol. 7 (Saga, #7)', 'Fortunately, the Milk...', 'The Love Interest']?", "answer": "The Black Monday Murders, Vol. 1: All Hail, God Mammon"}
{"qid": "238", "question": "What book should be recommended to the user based on his history: ['Hidden Hollywood (Happy Endings Book Club, #1)', 'Way Down Deep', 'Beautiful Mistake', '#famous', \"My Best Friend's Ex\"]?", "answer": "After the Game (The Field Party, #3)"}
{"qid": "239", "question": "What book should be recommended to the user based on his history: ['How to Murder the Man of Your Dreams (Ellie Haskell Mystery, #6)', 'Atlas Shrugged', 'Death at Dovecote Hatch: A 1930s Country House Murder Mystery', 'creating memories by Jacqueline Gillam Fairchild (book one)']?", "answer": "Creating Memories -book one of the Scrap Book Trilogy"}
